# **SUNDAY TOYIN**

No 24, Roadmaker, Akure, Ondo State. 📞 07039258061

✓ oluwatoyinsunday93@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Highly organized, people-oriented individual with outstanding skills and expertise gained through 4+ years of working experience. Experienced in providing customer service to clients, conducting cash consolidation on a daily basis, preparing daily branch reports, and reconciling transactions according to the bank's procedures. Proven ability to offer guidance and assistance to the customers of a company in order to maximize loyalty and satisfaction. Handled 25+ customer transactions per hour, resolved 130+ customer accounts issues weekly, increased customer satisfaction by 10% in 6 months, and managed cash and records effectively.

## **CORE SKILLS AND COMPETENCE**

- Highly organized, detail-oriented, and result driven, and possess effective leadership, communication, analytical, teamwork, adaptability, time management and problem-solving skills.
- Outstanding ability to deliver high quality performance, focus on details and ensure accuracy.
- Excellent ability to maintain a high level of confidentiality, help improve processes and support organizational growth and development.
- Strong ability to multitask, and can ensure excellent service delivery without compromising standards.
- Excellent ability to create and maintain rapport, build effective customer relationships and ensure client satisfaction.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **TELLER**

|DECEMBER 2019 - FEBRUARY 2021|

## UBA, Adeyemi College of Education, Ondo State.

- Processed standard teller transactions for customers including servicing client accounts, accepting loan payments, managing safe deposit box payments, cashing checks, balancing cash drawers, handling night deposits, correcting discrepancies.
- Assisted with the training of 2 new tellers ensuring that they received a comprehensive education on proper banking policies.
- ♦ Handled 25+ customer transactions per hour with extreme attention to detail, and responded to customer account inquiries totaling 130+ weekly accounts.

## **ECONOMICS EDUCATOR (NYSC)**

|OCTOBER 2018 - OCTOBER 2019|

### Day Secondary School, Army Barracks, Jubia, Katsina State.

- Created lesson plans on Economics as a subject and taught creatively using various modern teaching techniques which resulted in easy assimilation in students.
- Led and administered terminal tests and examinations with recorded pass marks of 85%, and ensured error-free recording of students' scores.
- Recommended new teaching methods for the improvement in academic grades of the students.

## **CUSTOMER SERVICE OFFICER**

|SEPTEMBER 2014 - OCTOBER 2015|

Cherries Gift and Supermarket, Lagos State.

### **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

Monitoring and evaluation

Organization & prioritization

Inventory management

Database management

Administrative support

Teaching and learning

Curriculum building

Accounts handling.

Customer service

Problem-solving

Record keeping

Cash handling

Supervision

Leadership

Scheduling

Research

#### **LANGUAGE**

English, Yoruba

## **GENDER**

Female

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

MS Office

- Provided customer service in person and over the phone, and effectively managed time to improve overall customer experience.
- Implemented new customer service strategies successfully, increasing customer satisfaction by 10% in 6 months.
- Operated POS cash register, handled an average of 92 transactions daily, and counted money in cash drawers to ensure the amount was correct.
- Managed money effectively and reported transactions in personal records and company databases.

## **WARD ATTENDANT (SIWES)**

|MARCH 2013 - JUNE 2013|

State Specialist Hospital, Akure, Ondo State.

- Maintained positive public relations and administered decisions by ethical principles.
- Communicated effectively with members of the health care team and ensured to participate in quality improvement.
- Participated in team spirit and unit morale concerns and maintained a safe work environment.

#### **CLASS EDUCATOR**

**|JUNE 2012 - SEPTEMBER 2013|** 

Prestige Nursery and Primary School, Ondo State.

- Organised learning materials, planned lessons and taught creatively using various modern teaching techniques which resulted in easy assimilation in students.
- Conducted extra-mural classes for students who were not fast learners and it resulted in easy grasping of the French subject.
- Collaborated with other teaching staff to help ensure smooth run of daily academic activities.

### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

HIGHER NATIONAL DIPLOMA (HND) IN NUTRITION & DIETETICS | 2018 | Rufus Giwa Polytechnic, Ondo State.

NATIONAL DIPLOMA (ND) IN NUTRITION & DIETETICS |2014|

Rufus Giwa Polytechnic, Ondo State.

NATIONAL EXAMINATION COUNCIL |2012|

Dynamic International College, Ondo State.

### **REFERENCE**

Available on request